Guide to the Presidential inauguration programs, 1867-2016.
Presidential inauguration programs, 1867-2016.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Presidential inauguration programs, 1867-2016.
47-4-1290
Cornell University.
.3 cubic ft.
Printed material and videos.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Programs for inauguration ceremonies of Cornell University presidents; includes invitations, congratulatory certificates, and guest lists from the inauguration of Frank H. T. Rhodes and videos.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Programs for inauguration ceremonies of Cornell University presidents; includes invitations, congratulatory certificates, and guest lists from the inauguration of Frank H. T. Rhodes, November 10, 1977. Also includes programs and addresses for Andrew Dickson White, Charles Kendall Adams, Jacob Gould Schurman, Livingston Farrand, Edmund Ezra Day, Deane W. Malott, Dale R. Corson, James Alfred Perkins, Hunter Ripley Rawlings III, Jeffrey S. Lehman, David J. Skorton, and Elizabeth Garrett. Also videos.
Includes an inaugural program for Hunter Rawlings signed by Rawlings, Rhodes, Corson, Perkins, and Malott.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Adams, Charles Kendall, 1835-1902.; Corson, Dale R., 1914-2012.; Day, Edmund Ezra, 1883-1951.; Farrand, Livingston, 1867-1939.; Garrett, Elizabeth, 1963-2016.; Lehman, Jeffrey S.; Malott, Deane W. (Deane Waldo), 1898-1996.; Perkins, James Alfred, 1911-1998.; Rawlings, Hunter R.; Rhodes, Frank Harold Trevor.; Schurman, Jacob Gould, 1854-1942.; Skorton, David J.; White, Andrew Dickson, 1832-1918.; Cornell University -- Presidents.; Cornell University
Subjects:
Presidents
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Andrew Dickson White
Box 1
Series II. Charles Kendall Adams
Box 1
Series III. Jacob Gould Schurman
Box 1
Series IV. Livingston Farrand
Box 1
Series V. Edmund Ezra Day
Box 1
Series VI. Deane Waldo Malott
Box 1
Series VII. James Alfred Perkins
Box 1
Series VIII. Dale R. Corson
Box 1
Series IX. Frank H. T. Rhodes
Boxes 1
Series X. Hunter R. Rawlings III
Box 1
Series XI. Jeffrey S. Lehman
Boxes 1
Series XII. David Skorton
Boxes 1
Series XIII. Elizabeth Garrett
Box 1
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Andrew Dickson White
  - Andrew Dickson White inauguration, 1868-10-07, 1921 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Includes two programs, two "reprints from the account of the proceedings at the Inauguration", and a photocopy of A.D. White's address
- Series II. Charles Kendall Adams
  - Charles Kendall Adams inauguration, 1885-11-19-1886 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Includes an invitation to the inauguration, a program, two copies of "Proceedings and Addresses as the Inauguration of Charles Kendall Adams", and a photocopy of the Cornell Era from November 20, 1885
- Series III. Jacob Gould Shurman
  - Jacob Gould Schurman inauguration, 1892-11-11 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Includes copy of "Inauguration of President Schurman" and photocopied excerpt of book
- Series IV. Livingston Farrand
  - Livingston Farrand inauguration, 1921-06-30-1921-10-20 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Includes two programs, program for inaugural dinner, information pamphlet for those participating in ceremony, in a copy of "Inauguration of Livingston Farrand Fourth President of Cornell University" and photocopied excerpt of book and Alumni news
- Series V. Edmund Ezra Day
  - Edmund Ezra Day inauguration, 1936-11-12-1937-10-08 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Includes inauguration ticket, and photocopied excerpt of book and Alumni news
- Series VI. Deane Waldo Malott
  - Deane Waldo Malott inauguration, 1951-02-1951-10-15 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Includes photocopied program and two photocopied articles from Alumni news
- Series VII. James Alfred Perkins
  - James Alfred Perkins inauguration, 1963-10-04 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Includes an invitation, two programs, program for inaugural lunch, two copies of "Inauguration of James Alfred Perkins", and information regarding the University Mace and Baton - first used in Perkins inauguration
- Series VIII. Dale R. Corson
  - Dale R. Corson inauguration, 1969-10-1970-06-08, 1976-06 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Includes program for inaugural dinner, information about guests and menu for dinner, Commencement and Investiture of the President program, note from Corson's office explaining why his inauguration took place when it did, inaugural address, photocopied pages from Ithaca Journal, and photocopied article from Alumni news
- Series IX. Frank H. T. Rhodes
  - Frank H. T. Rhodes inauguration, 1977-11-10 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Series X. Hunter R. Rawlings III
  - Hunter R. Rawlings III inauguration, 1995; DVD-2109 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Series XI. Jeffrey S. Lehman
  - Lehman inauguration inauguration, 2003-10-16 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Series XII. David Skorton
  - David Skorton, 2006-09-07 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Includes inaugural address
- Series XIII. Elizabeth Garrett
  - Elizabeth Garrett, 2015-09-18 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Includes program and inaugural address
- Series XIV. Martha Pollack
  - Martha Pollack, 2015-09-18 (Box 1, Folder 14)